

BRETONES

FULL STACK DEVELOPER & GRAPHIC DESIGNER

wola@alexbretones.com

+34 675 273 454

linkedin.com/in/abretones

www.alexbretones.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Current position November 2018

Current position

February 2018

FRONTEND & WEB DEVELOPER

▼ Barcelona at Altran Components design & development with handlebars & sass.

UI & WEB DEV TEACHER ASSISTANT

at Ironhack ▼ Barcelona Web Development course: HTML, CSS, JS, Canvas, Express.js, Node.js, Handlebars.js, Angular, React, Redux. UX/UI course: visual concept and design with sketch.

2015 - 2018 **DESIGNER & DEVELOPER FREELANCE**

> at alexbretones com Rarcelona Branding, Web & Editorial Design, Motion Graphics. HTML, CSS, JS, Angular, React, Node.js, Express.js.

2017 - 2018 **DESIGN / FRONTEND INSTRUCTOR**

> at Salessians Sarrià & Tadel Formació Barcelona Instructor for the Visual Design module for the 2017 Multimedia Publishing Projects course and Web Dev Course in two different schools.

2015 - 2017 **GRAPHIC AND WEB DESIGNER**

> at Estudio WAY Barcelona Estudio WAY is a personal project, a design studio based in Barcelona and specialized in branding identity, web design (CMS, HTML5 and CSS3), UX/UI, Usability and editorial design.

GRAPHIC AND VISUAL DESIGNER 2015

> at Mailify Barcelona Newsletter templates design.

2015 - 2013 **HEAD OF MARKETING & COMMUNICATION**

Barcelona at U.E. Cornellà

BACKGROUND

I am a graphic designer with a Master Degree in Business Management (Universitat de Barcelona), a Postdegree in Ecommerce (Seeway) and a Master Degree in Graphic Design and Digital Art (Seeway).

I also have a Degree in Education which allowed me to teach design in different schools in Barcelona. I just finished Ironhack Web Development parttime learning full stack technologies, I believe that both, my design experience aligned with my education in Full-Stack Development will allow me to grow into a more proficient and complete designer professional.

SKILLS





EDUCATION

2017

2012

THE COMPLETE REACT FULL STACK COURSE 2018 at Udemy

Online **FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT**

at Ironhack ▼ Barcelona Front-end Development (Javascript, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3, GIT and Github). Mean Stack Back-end (Node.Js, Express.js and MongoDB). Microservices with Angular2 (APIs with Node.Js and MVC with Angular2).

MASTER DEGREE IN GRAPHIC DESIGN & DIGITAL ART 2015

Offline Design (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign and Brand Identity).

Online Design (HTML5, CSS3, UI/UX, Digital Marketing and Web Environment). Motion Graphics (Audio Visual Lenguage and After Effects).

POSTGRADUATE DEGREE IN ECOMMERCE 2015

> Barcelona at Seeway Google Analytics, Prestashop, Magento / Online Marketing Plan.

MASTER DEGREE IN SPORTS BUSINESS MANAGEMENT 2013

at Universitat de Barcelona ▼ Barcelona Business analysis, Sports Marketing and Research, Events Organization, Market Opportunities, Legal Framework.

WEB DESIGN WITH HTML5 AND CSS3 2013

at SeisCocos Technical School

DEGREE IN SPORTS EDUCATION

at Universidad de Almería

♥ Almería

Málaga

Adobe Suite Sketch HTML, CSS & IS Angular React + Redux Node.js **Express** MongoDB Wordpress UX / UI / Usability Cinema 4D / Blender

LANGUAGES

Spanish Native English Fluent French Basic Catalan Intermediate Portuguese Basic